Andre Silva Macedo

24 years old, Brazilian

Rua Caldas da Rainha Belo Horizonte Brazil >>> +55 (31) 99838-5766 \squares contato@andremacedo.dev

Education

2016–2019 Bachelor, FUMEC University, Belo Horizonte - Brazil, Computer Science.

About me

A dedicated full-stack developer with 4 years of experience in software development. Polyglot programming skills in Java, Node.js and Python. Experience with software development of a new product, from the idea to the delivery. As well as experience in maintenance and refactoring of existing software.

Experience

2020-present **Software Architect and Developer**, *Seidor Véritas*, Belo Horizonte.

Responsible for the deploy of the whole infraestructure using infra as code (aws-cdk). Infra composed by Elastic Beanstalk, ECS, Fargate, Lambda, API Gateway, and more.

2019–2020 **Software Developer**, *Seidor Véritas*, Belo Horizonte.

Designed and developed REST micro-services and AWS Lambdas using Node.js and Java. Development heavily focused in automated tests (unit and integration tests) and API documentation since the API is used by external clients.

2018–2019 Full-stack Developer, Melhor Voo, Belo Horizonte.

Developed various web pages and components using Node.js, React.js, Redux and JSS; Designed and implemented RESTful APIs using Express.js, Laravel and Django Rest Framework; Worked with MySQL and MongoDB databases; Developed web crawlers using Node.js and Python.

2016–2018 **Full-stack Java Developer**, *Registrocom.com*, Belo Horizonte.

Developed mostly web applications using Java 7, JSF 2.2 and 2, Primefaces 6 and 3, JPA (Hibernate and Eclipselink), MySQL and Apache Tomcat 8.

2014–2016 **IT Support**, *SMTE Construções e Montagens*, Belo Horizonte.

Maintenance of the internal network and work stations; Installation and configuration of CCTV; Network Certification.

Knowledge

Frontend React, Primefaces

Backend Node.js, Python, Java

Frameworks Express, Fastify, Django, Flask, Spring

Databases MySQL, Postgres, MongoDB, DynamoDB

AWS Lambda, Step Functions, ECS, Fargate, EC2, Elastic Beanstalk, S3, API Gateway, Lambda Authorizers, RDS, Cognito, SQS, CodeBuild, CodePipeline, CDK

Other Linux, Git, Scrum, Automated Tests

Languages

Portuguese Native

English Full professional proficiency